EMERSSON CHEW

7 Barnacle Rise, Auckland, Red Beach 0932 ◆ 0220377088 ◆ emerssonchewcs@gmail.com www.emerssonchew.com ◆ www.linkedin.com/in/emersson-chew

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A well rounded professional with technical skills ranging from software architecture, web development, and user experience design to business skills like social media networks for business, information systems and e-commerce for organisations, and management information systems.

SKILLS

- Requirements Gathering and Analysis
- User Experience Design
- Front-End Web Development
- Management Information Systems
- System Management and Testing

WORK HISTORY

Finance Assistant, Jan 2018 to Mar 2018

BODCO Ltd – Hamilton

Finance

- Update entries in the company's system using SAP Business ByDesign
- Liaise with other departments to prepare information for the end of financial year external audit, sales and operations plan, cost reduction plan and reports for management.

<u>IT</u>

- Provide training on SAP Business ByDesign procedures and processes
- Evaluate new IT equipment and suggest purchase options
- Configure new and reconfigure current IT equipment
- Create and maintain an IT equipment register list

Administration

• Create, review and merge company policies i.e. IT Policies, HR Policies, Communications Policies, Social Media Policies, etc.

Web Developer, Oct 2016 to June 2017

Freelance - Auckland

- Learn how to use a website creation service (Wix) to create two websites for businesses
- Learn how to create a high fidelity prototype of a website from scratch for a user experience design project in university
- All projects are available on www.emerssonchew.com

EDUCATION

2015 – 2017: Bachelor of Information Science: Major in Information Technology and Minor in Information Systems at **Massey University**